Guide to the North Carolina State University School of Design Historic Architecture Research Project Records, 1951-1976 UA 110.041
Special Collections Research Center
- UA 110.041 Series 1: Projects, 1951-1976; 32.75 linear feet 369 flat folders, 23 archival boxes, and 1 archival half box
  - New Jersey, Essex County, Newark: High Service Reservoir Drawings, 15 drawings (Folder 181.1)
  - New Jersey, Essex County, Newark: High Service Reservoir Field notes, photographs (Box 9, Folder 181.2)
  - Delaware, New Castle County: DuPont Residence & Black Powder Rolling Mill Drawings, 9 drawings (Folder 182.1)
  - Delaware, New Castle County: DuPont Residence & Black Powder Rolling Mill Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 9, Folder 182.2)
  - North Carolina, Macon County, Franklin: St. Agnes Episcopal Church Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 183.1)
  - North Carolina, Macon County, Franklin: St. Agnes Episcopal Church Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 9, Folder 183.2)
  - North Carolina, New Hanover County, Wilmington: Cornwallis House [Burgwin-Wright house] Drawings, 10 drawings (Folder 184.1)
  - North Carolina, New Hanover County, Wilmington: Cornwallis House [Burgwin-Wright house] Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 9, Folder 184.2)
  - North Carolina, Halifax County, Littleton: Mosby Hall (Little Manor) Drawings, 10 drawings (Folder 185.1)
  - North Carolina, Halifax County, Littleton: Mosby Hall (Little Manor) Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 9, Folder 185.2)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: St. Matthew's Episcopal Church Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 186.1)
  - Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 9, Folder 186.2)
  - North Carolina, Rowan County, Salisbury: Henderson Law Office Drawings, 11 drawings (Folder 187.1)
  - North Carolina, Rowan County, Salisbury: Henderson Law Office Field notes, photographs (Box 9, Folder 187.2)
  - North Carolina, Northampton County, Rich Square: Lawrence Place/The Shoulars Farm Drawings, 15 drawings (Folder 188.1)
  - North Carolina, Northampton County, Rich Square: Lawrence Place/The Shoulars Farm Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 9, Folder 188.2)
  - Maryland, Baltimore: Lloyd Street Synagogue Drawings, 10 drawings (Folder 189.1)
  - Maryland, Baltimore: Lloyd Street Synagogue Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 9, Folder 189.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: St. Ambrose Episcopal Church Drawings, 7 drawings (Folder 190.1)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: St. Ambrose Episcopal Church Field notes, photographs (Box 9, Folder 190.2)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Paquinett House Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 191.1)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Paquinett House Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 9, Folder 191.2)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Hammock House Drawings, 9 drawings (Folder 192.1)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Hammock House Field notes, photographs (Box 9, Folder 192.2)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Morse House [drawings and field notes missing] (Box 9, Folder 193)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Rumley House Field notes, photographs, negatives [drawings missing], 0 drawings (Box 9, Folder 194.1)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Easton House Drawings, 11 drawings (Folder 195.1)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Easton House Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 9, Folder 195.2)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Hancock House Drawings, 6 drawings (Folder 196.1)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Hancock House Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 10, Folder 196.2)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Nelson House Field notes, photographs, negative [drawings missing], 0 drawings (Box 10, Folder 197.1)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Balsum House Drawings, 7 drawings (Folder 198.1)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Balsum House Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 10, Folder 198.2)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Piver (Jesse) House Drawings, 10 drawings (Folder 199.1)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Piver (Jesse) House Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 10, Folder 199.2)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Duncan House Field notes, photographs, negatives [drawings missing], 0 drawings (Box 10, Folder 200.1)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Taylor House Drawings, 9 drawings (Folder 201.1)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Taylor House Field notes (Box 10, Folder 201.2)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Cramer House Field notes, photographs, negative [drawings missing], 0 drawings (Box 10, Folder 202.1)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Historical Background of the City of Beaufort Drawings, 21 drawings (Folder 203.1)
  - North Carolina, Forsyth County, Bethania: Jones Plantation Barn (now at Old Salem) [same as project 372] Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 204.1)
  - North Carolina, Forsyth County, Bethania: Jones Plantation Barn (now at Old Salem) [same as project 372] Field notes, photograph (Box 10, Folder 204.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh vicinity: Midway Plantation Drawings, 34 drawings (Folder 205.1)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh vicinity: Midway Plantation Field notes (Box 10, Folder 205.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Fourth Dormitory, N.C. State College Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 206.1)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Fourth Dormitory, N.C. State College Field notes, photographs (Box 10, Folder 206.2)
  - Tennessee, Knox County, Knoxville vicinity: Ramsey House Drawings, 14 drawings (Folder 207.1)
  - Tennessee, Knox County, Knoxville vicinity: Ramsey House Field notes (Box 10, Folder 207.2)
  - North Carolina, Rowan County, Salisbury: First Presbyterian Church Drawings, 29 drawings (Folder 208.1)
  - North Carolina, Rowan County, Salisbury: First Presbyterian Church Oversized sketches (Folder 208.2)
  - North Carolina, Rowan County, Salisbury: First Presbyterian Church Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 10, Folder 208.3)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: American Legion Building Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 209.1)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: American Legion Building Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 10, Folder 209.2)
  - North Carolina, Pitt County, Greenville: Rountree Farmhouse Drawings, 9 drawings (Folder 210.1)
  - North Carolina, Pitt County, Greenville: Rountree Farmhouse Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 10, Folder 210.2)
  - North Carolina, Pender County, Hampstead: Sloop Point Plantation Drawings, 12 drawings (Folder 211.1)
  - North Carolina, Pender County, Hampstead: Sloop Point Plantation Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 10, Folder 211.2)
  - North Carolina, Pasquotank County, Weeksville: St. John's Episcopal Church Drawings, 10 drawings (Folder 212.1)
  - North Carolina, Pasquotank County, Weeksville: St. John's Episcopal Church Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 11, Folder 212.2)
  - North Carolina, Guilford County, Greensboro: Bumpass House [same as project 38] Drawings, 10 drawings (Folder 213.1)
  - North Carolina, Guilford County, Greensboro: Bumpas House [same as project 38] Field notes, photograph, negative (Box 11, Folder 213.2)
  - North Carolina, Harnett County, Lillington vicinity: Summervilla Drawings, 10 drawings (Folder 214.1)
  - North Carolina, Harnett County, Lillington vicinity: Summervilla Field notes, photograph, negative (Box 11, Folder 214.2)
  - North Carolina, Randolph County, Franklinville: Julian House Drawings, 10 drawings (Folder 215.1)
  - North Carolina, Randolph County, Franklinville: Julian House Oversized sketches (Folder 215.2)
  - North Carolina, Randolph County, Franklinville: Julian House Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 11, Folder 215.3)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: Hillsborough Site Studies Drawings, 20 drawings (Folder 216.1)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: Hillsborough Site Studies Map of Hillsborough, 1863 (blue line print) (Box 11, Folder 216.2)
  - North Carolina, Mecklenburg County, Crab Orchard township: White Oak Plantation Drawings, 14 drawings (Folder 217.1)
  - North Carolina, Mecklenburg County, Crab Orchard township: White Oak Plantation Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 11, Folder 217.2)
  - North Carolina, Catawba County, Hickory: Joe Wilson House Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 218.1)
  - North Carolina, Catawba County, Hickory: Joe Wilson House Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 11, Folder 218.2)
  - North Carolina, Northampton County, Jackson: Verona, Matt Ransom Estate Drawings, 10 drawings (Folder 219.1)
  - North Carolina, Northampton County, Jackson: Verona, Matt Ransom Estate Field notes, photograph, negative (Box 11, Folder 219.2)
  - North Carolina, Lenoir County, Kinston: Heritage House Drawings, 13 drawings (Folder 220.1)
  - North Carolina, Lenoir County, Kinston: Heritage House Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 11, Folder 220.2)
  - North Carolina, Lincoln County, Maiden: St. Matthew's Church Arbor Drawings, 7 drawings (Folder 221.1)
  - North Carolina, Lincoln County, Maiden: St. Matthew's Church Arbor Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 11, Folder 221.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Christ Episcopal Church Drawings, 20 drawings (Folder 222.1)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Christ Episcopal Church Field notes (Box 11, Folder 222.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Christ Episcopal Church Photographs, negatives (Box 11, Folder 222.3)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: Chatwood-- The Coach House Drawings, 9 drawings (Folder 223.1)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: Chatwood-- The Coach House Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 11, Folder 223.2)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: Webb House Kitchen Drawings, 9 drawings (Folder 224.1)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: Webb House Kitchen Field notes, photograph, negative (Box 11, Folder 224.2)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: Hillsborough Methodist Church Drawings, 16 drawings (Folder 225.1)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: Hillsborough Methodist Church Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 11, Folder 225.2)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: Murphy House Drawings, 14 drawings (Folder 226.1)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: Murphy House Oversized sketches (Folder 226.2)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: Murphy House Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 12, Folder 226.3)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: Patterson-Palmer House Drawings, 11 drawings (Folder 227.1)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: Patterson-Palmer House Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 12, Folder 227.2)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: San Souci Plantation Drawings, 16 drawings (Folder 228.1)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: San Souci Plantation Oversized sketches (Folder 228.2)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: San Souci Plantation Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 12, Folder 228.3)
  - North Carolina, Stanly County, Palmersville: Eddings Boarding House Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 229.1)
  - North Carolina, Stanly County, Palmersville: Eddings Boarding House Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 12, Folder 229.2)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: Peter Browne Ruffin Homestead Drawings, 13 drawings (Folder 230.1)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: Peter Browne Ruffin Homestead Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 12, Folder 230.2)
  - North Carolina, Forsyth County, Clemmons: Old Clemmons Inn (Ogburn Residence) Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 231.1)
  - North Carolina, Forsyth County, Clemmons: Old Clemmons Inn (Ogburn Residence) Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 12, Folder 231.2)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Essay on the City of Beaufort: Beaufort, North Carolina in 1800" by Reyhan Tansal, (with notes, maps, photographs), 0 drawings (Box 12, Folder 232.1)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: Ayr Mount Drawings, 20 drawings (Folder 233.1)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: Ayr Mount Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 12, Folder 233.2)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: Ayr Mount Oversized sketches (Folder 233.3)
  - North Carolina, Cumberland County, Fayetteville: Kyle House Drawings, 17 drawings (Folder 234.1)
  - North Carolina, Cumberland County, Fayetteville: Kyle House Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 12, Folder 234.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Forestville: Chappell Residence Drawings, 18 drawings (Folder 235.1)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Forestville: Chappell Residence Oversized sketches (Folder 235.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Forestville: Chappell Residence Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 12, Folder 235.3)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Hatsell House Field notes, photographs, negative [drawings missing], 0 drawings (Box 12, Folder 236.1)
  - North Carolina, Franklin County, Rocky Ford community: Foster House Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 237.1)
  - North Carolina, Franklin County, Rocky Ford community: Foster House Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 12, Folder 237.2)
  - Pennsylvania, Montgomery County, Valley Forge: Knox's Bridge Drawings, 7 drawings (Folder 238.1)
  - Pennsylvania, Montgomery County, Valley Forge: Knox's Bridge Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 12, Folder 238.2)
  - West Virginia, Fayette County, Ansted: Tyree Tavern Drawings, 10 drawings (Folder 239.1)
  - Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 12, Folder 239.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Hinsdale House Oversized sketches, 32 drawings (Folder 240.1)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Hinsdale House Field notes (Box 12, Folder 240.2)
  - North Carolina, Catawba County, Claremont vicinity: Bunker Hill Covered Bridge over Lyle Creek [same as project no. 119] Drawings, 10 drawings (Folder 241.1)
  - North Carolina, Catawba County, Claremont vicinity: Bunker Hill Covered Bridge over Lyle Creek [same as project no. 119] Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 12, Folder 241.2)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Bell House Field notes, photograph [drawings missing], 0 drawings (Box 12, Folder 242.1)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Chapel Hill: Gerrard Hall, UNC Drawings, 9 drawings (Folder 243.1)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Chapel Hill: Gerrard Hall, UNC Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 13, Folder 243.2)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Chapel Hill: Old East & Person Hall, UNC Drawings, 12 drawings (Folder 244.1)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Chapel Hill: Old East & Person Hall, UNC Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 13, Folder 244.2)
  - North Carolina, Guilford County, Jamestown: Mendenhall House Drawings, 10 drawings (Folder 245.1)
  - North Carolina, Guilford County, Jamestown: Mendenhall House Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 13, Folder 245.2)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Pigott House Drawings, 11 drawings (Folder 246.1)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Pigott House Field notes, photographs (Box 13, Folder 246.2)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Chapel Hill: New East, UNC Drawings, 16 drawings (Folder 247.1)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Chapel Hill: New East, UNC Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 13, Folder 247.2)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: Maplewood Drawings, 10 drawings (Folder 248.1)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: Maplewood Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 13, Folder 248.2)
  - North Carolina, Granville County, Oxford vicinity: Hill Airy Drawings, 11 drawings (Folder 249.1)
  - North Carolina, Granville County, Oxford vicinity: Hill Airy Field notes, photograph, negative (Box 13, Folder 249.2)
  - North Carolina, Bertie County: Mount Gould Drawings, 12 drawings (Folder 250.1)
  - North Carolina, Bertie County: Mount Gould Oversized sketches (Folder 250.2)
  - North Carolina, Bertie County: Mount Gould Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 13, Folder 250.3)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: White House Drawings, 10 drawings (Folder 251.1)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: White House Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 13, Folder 251.2)
  - Ohio, Lake County, Painesville: Mathews House Drawings, 14 drawings (Folder 252.1)
  - Ohio, Lake County, Painesville: Mathews House Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 13, Folder 252.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Apex/Cary vicinity: Bennett House & Farm [a.k.a. Joseph Lane House, same as project 20] Drawings, 15 drawings (Folder 253.1)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Apex/Cary vicinity: Bennett House & Farm [a.k.a. Joseph Lane House, same as project 20] Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 13, Folder 253.2)
  - North Carolina, Warren County, Warrenton: Emmanuel Episcopal Church Drawings, 11 drawings (Folder 254.1)
  - North Carolina, Warren County, Warrenton: Emmanuel Episcopal Church Oversized sketches (Folder 254.2)
  - North Carolina, Warren County, Warrenton: Emmanuel Episcopal Church Field notes, photograph, negative (Box 13, Folder 254.3)
  - North Carolina, Caswell County, Yanceyville: Dongola Drawings, 11 drawings (Folder 255.1)
  - North Carolina, Caswell County, Yanceyville: Dongola Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 13, Folder 255.2)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Chapel Hill: New West, UNC Drawings, 21 drawings (Folder 256.1)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Chapel Hill: New West, UNC Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 14, Folder 256.2)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: Moorefields Drawings, 16 drawings (Folder 257.1)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: Moorefields Field notes, photograph, negatives (Box 14, Folder 257.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Haywood Hall Drawings, 21 drawings (Folder 258.1)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Haywood Hall Field notes, photograph, negative (Box 14, Folder 258.2)
  - North Carolina, Franklin County: Old Collin's Place Drawings, 14 drawings (Folder 259.1)
  - North Carolina, Franklin County: Old Collin's Place Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 14, Folder 259.2)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Longest House Drawings, 9 drawings (Folder 260.1)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Longest House Field notes, photograph, negative (Box 14, Folder 260.2)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Old Burying Ground Drawings, 12 drawings (Folder 261.1)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Old Burying Ground Field notes (Box 14, Folder 261.2)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Davis House Drawings, 14 drawings (Folder 262.1)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Davis House Field notes (Box 14, Folder 262.2)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Davis House Photographs, negatives (Box 14, Folder 262.3)
  - North Carolina, Edgecombe County, Tarboro vicinity: Coolmore Farm (Powell House)Field notes, photograph [drawings missing], 0 drawings (Box 14, Folder 263.1)
  - District of Columbia, Washington [Georgetown]: Oak Hill Cemetery Chapel Drawings (Folder 264.1)
  - District of Columbia, Washington [Georgetown]: Oak Hill Cemetery Chapel Field notes (Box 14, Folder 264.2)
  - District of Columbia, Washington [Georgetown]: Oak Hill Cemetery Chapel Photographs, negatives, color slides (Box 14, Folder 264.3)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Elmwood Drawings, 15 drawings (Folder 265.1)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Elmwood Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 14, Folder 265.2)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: Dr. D.H. Moore House Drawings, 19 drawings (Folder 266.1)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: Dr. D.H. Moore House Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 15, Folder 266.2)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Beaufort High School Drawings, 13 drawings (Folder 267.1)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Beaufort High School Field notes, photograph, negative (Box 15, Folder 267.2)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Old Beaufort Jail Drawings, 12 drawings (Folder 268.1)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Old Beaufort Jail Field notes, photographs (Box 15, Folder 268.2)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Leecraft (Benjamin) House Drawings, 13 drawings (Folder 269.1)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Leecraft (Benjamin) House Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 15, Folder 269.2)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Piver (William) House Drawings, 17 drawings (Folder 270.1)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Piver (William) House Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 15, Folder 270.2)
  - North Carolina, Guilford County, Greensboro: Dunleith Drawings, 29 drawings (Folder 271.1)
  - North Carolina, Guilford County, Greensboro: Dunleith Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 15, Folder 271.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County: Norwood Plantation Drawings, 28 drawings (Folder 272.1)
  - North Carolina, Wake County: Norwood Plantation Field notes, photographs (Box 15, Folder 272.2)
  - Maryland, Charles County, Port Tobacco vicinity: Chandler's Hope Drawings, 21 drawings (Folder 273.1)
  - Maryland, Charles County, Port Tobacco vicinity: Chandler's Hope Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 15, Folder 273.2)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Fuller House Drawings, 11 drawings (Folder 274.1)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Fuller House Field notes, photograph, negative (Box 15, Folder 274.2)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Piver (Peter) House Drawings, 11 drawings (Folder 275.1)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Piver (Peter) House Field notes, photograph, negatives (Box 15, Folder 275.2)
  - North Carolina, Guilford County: Haley's Inn Drawings, 9 drawings (Folder 276.1)
  - North Carolina, Guilford County: Haley's Inn Field notes, photographs (Box 15, Folder 276.2)
  - North Carolina, Buncombe County, Fairview vicinity: Sherrill's Inn Drawings, 20 drawings (Folder 277.1)
  - North Carolina, Buncombe County, Fairview vicinity: Sherrill's Inn Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 15, Folder 277.2)
  - North Carolina, Halifax County, Enfield vicinity: Cedar Grove (Whittaker House) Drawings, 20 drawings (Folder 278.1)
  - North Carolina, Halifax County, Enfield vicinity: Cedar Grove (Whittaker House) Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 16, Folder 278.2)
  - North Carolina, Mecklenburg County, Davidson: Oak and Elm Rows, Davidson College Drawings, 9 drawings (Folder 279.1)
  - North Carolina, Mecklenburg County, Davidson: Oak and Elm Rows, Davidson College Field notes, photographs (Box 16, Folder 279.2)
  - North Carolina, Mecklenburg County, Davidson: Carolina Inn Drawings, 13 drawings (Folder 280.1)
  - North Carolina, Mecklenburg County, Davidson: Carolina Inn Field notes, photograph, negative (Box 16, Folder 280.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Captain Lee House Drawings, 20 drawings (Folder 281.1)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Captain Lee House Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 16, Folder 281.2)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Concordia Lodge Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 282.1)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: Concordia Lodge Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 16, Folder 282.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Lewis House [a.k.a. Lewis-Smith House] Drawings, 11 drawings (Folder 283.1)